A good friend to meet, MBC
You know, a fun party
about ten years
Smaller than mountain roots
The kids in the mountains were hitting me with sticks and fanning me.
Another thing while shaking
A stage that brings humor to the class
You know, I did that too.
I was chosen as the main character
It's Cinderella
Because it's pretty
I wasn't chosen as Cinderella.
You were good at rock, paper, scissors.
The prettiest person in our class
I am Seyoung
I heard you measured it with a treasure trove.
Well anyway
Because I’m a princess now too
nice dress
I guess I'll try it on
I was just excited
Mom said so
Wear it only once at a party.
Buy something like a dress
I can't give it to you
Haha, so in the end
I was pushed out of the way
And then on a dark stage
I'm wondering in the corner
Ah, I think I noticed it right then.
I live my whole life
As the main character, I'm not trying to make a living.
A corner of the stage where you can no longer be pushed away
That's the only thing
What I can have in my life
my only moxie
I think it will work out
But what
It helped me live
i my
I know where to stay
It's like understanding a topic while working.
I heard you well um
Now next time
A story that happened when I bought a key
Let me solve it
Let’s tell some story again, you guys sit down
Why are you sitting? It's Sunday night.
If I wake up now
Oh, I have to go to work.
Don't sleep
Our weekend night
Don't just let me go like this, sister.
Uh, uh, sister, I absolutely hate the charge.
Ah, sister
Let's talk about anything else, that's it.
I'm going to sleep
You guys, stop holding on and go to sleep.
Don't do it, come back, comeback
Comeback Comeback Comeback
It happened when I was eight. Oh what?
I think it lacks a bit of flavor.
Cooking the dough
Is the degree a bit different?
Because I can’t use machines
The taste is a little different
I guess I'll have to endure it.
I'm sure you're having a hard time
Our class
With different concentrations
Just one more time
Let's try it ah
What's wrong kid
The child's name is
It's a founding anniversary event.
It's hard work
How many years has it been? Ah, the 30th anniversary.
30th anniversary celebration event
now
Because it's our 30th anniversary, our company's special
Thirty children who like snacks
I invited you
Ah, yes, I understand.
um
uh uh
Oh what should I do
Oh no no no
Oh, what should I do with this?
Please bring me some milk
Oh really
I'll bring something to wipe.
Oh wait just a moment
Wow Mr.
Oh wait a minute
Mr. Ani
Ah
What is it icy?
Would you like to eat dinner together later?
Pork cutlet restaurant in Namsan
I heard it's famous
Oh, I don't think it'll work because I'm busy.
Can I? Can I?
Richter Way Solait
Oh, you were busy yesterday too.
It was like that the other day too.
You can't keep avoiding me, right?
No, I like pork cutlet.
Yorley hehe
Yorlay hehe hoho lalalalala
Yorley
Because I was really busy yesterday too
Uh why not
Oh, I was really busy yesterday too.
go to hawaii
Please prepare for our event
Mike one to go cheki laut um
I kept holding back
Turn off autocomplete
You can't talk
child
This damn autocomplete is real.
what should i do
It's done, Mr.
Ichigo, at least wear this and go.
No, this is
Why does it look like this
Didn’t you go to that factory?
Why are you dressed like this?
Oh that's it
that
The owner overturned the sauce container.
Yeoborot is in the night room, so I'll come later.
I'm going to change.
Ah, I took that hand
I said it was a lot of work.
I didn't do it
uh that
Each and every one of them
Is it normal to do manual work?
Oh well, tomorrow anyway
invited
children are the best
You say you want to eat it?
Don Don Chip was released as a limited edition.
I'm not good at using machines
Although it's unfortunate
But what
Why am I the only one suffering?
I feel like I'm the only one who gets criticized
Who will receive the award tomorrow?
Geummo Attitude Excellence Award
Who saw it? You're giving me shit.
Oh, that's Dahye and Junseo
You also receive seeds.
within those three
There's an asshole
You should be thankful
I really spoke rudely
I'm just saying this because I'm talking about it.
I'm trying to be a bitch there
I know how much I worked hard
I really don't even know how thankful I am
Wait a minute
I don't want to receive the award.
Let’s just take it out, uh ah yes ah no
The delivery company
that
Dahye decided to contact you.
Ms. Dahye
Mr. Dahye
Oh Dahye
Where did you go
Ah
I'm filming a promotional video for the company.
I was chosen as that guy's model.
I said I would play the video at work tomorrow.
Who was that male model?
Team leader
Dr. Han
Uh hahahaha
It suits you well
It suits you really well
Pretty and handsome
They both know
That's right
These two match very well
Daishi said
Why is it called Princess of Malwon and Princess?
Now I understand
Even the princess
Uh uh uh uh
Wait uh uh
Oh my oh my
Oh sleep sleep sleep sleep just sleep
cut cut cut
Our man
Oh, this is a company promotional video.
But what is your expression right now?
Ah
Sangju wearing an armband at that banquet
It's like, oh, I almost bowed down.
I'm so sad
What should I do? It's done.
In the video
There will be a lot of voice actor comments.
Let me read it for you.
It fits there
Try making a facial expression.
happy necklace
The leading place for the right necklace
Ministry of Food and Drug Safety
Maron Where there is a burning camaraderie
But Maron
where my soul wants
bed in my room
Maron Maron
Let's live forever
Let's go together Maron, I love you Maron
Marron
Hahahahahaha
Like this
Look at your expression with affection.
With love for the company
Like this
Hehehe
Hey, I guess you're doing it as a trifecta, huh?
The future is not over yet
What are you again?
Hey Joo Hyeon-chul
yes no you
What do you do if you don't control people?
Uh uh ah
sorry
Baby, please go behind us.
Mr. Ha, hey there.
Please step back.
Oh, please step back.
Mother
Mother me
Oh wait a minute
Maybe
What did you recognize me?
Mother, today’s military
Does the restaurant serve pork cutlets?
Oh I want to die
It's so funny
Da-hee Jeong Da-hye Jeong
last letter
It's just one thing different
who is the princess
Who is your mother?
Oh what am I
I gave in 100 times and even got there.
I understand.
But
Look at me
Get away from me
Mom is so crazy haha
Smile no
Baby, that's right
I always dressed up a bit, huh?
What about people?
What you wear
If you look at what they wear, there are only two
I'm going there
Wow, he’s really living well.
I hope he lives well
I see you sometimes too
Oh, my own tower is like that.
Let’s die, it’s easier to die
I won't be embarrassed if I die
Now is not the time to die
It's time to change, yeah
salty
Made in Boutique Mother
shake cotton
It's 100% and I haven't even picked it up yet.
This will be a new, unopened product.
I'll lend you something special
no
What am I doing wearing this?
I heard you're having a party tomorrow.
It's not something the team prepares.
Hey, what kind of party is that?
I can't believe I don't like you.
I'm ordering you too, Mr.
I will definitely wear this tomorrow
Oh well, I'll get an award
finish
It's a perfect day for transformation.
Hey, what kind of action mask is this?
Transform yourself, sister
What about Dr. Han? Real-time search term
I'm a top-ranked person. What is that?
The main character of the fire
And the main character
This is how you meet the main character.
But you are like that now
um
No, Dr. Han, are you in your 60s?
They say pork cutlet is being served at a restaurant in the county today.
child
What kind of pork cutlet promotional ambassador are you?
Oh wait a minute
I heard that pork cutlet is coming out today.
Who? No, it was clear before.
Pork cutlet is good
But
The two of us ate together at a restaurant in the county.
Eating
Wouldn't it be a little strange?
some people
의심스럽게 볼 것 같은데
what doubts
no one doubts us
Hey hey
What is this?
Automatic stability
It's crazy again
Anyway, I had lunch.
Well then, that's it
Hey this
The rice looks like this, but how?
Even though it’s just tteokgalbi, would you like to give me one?
no it's okay
Thank you and take care of yourselves.
Oh Mr. Lee Jeong uh
uh
Oh why is this
Are you resigning? Yes.
That's how it happened
Ah
You didn't extend that contract.
It's not that I didn't do it, it's that I couldn't do it.
You know
Oh yes
No but
A company dinner when you leave the company
I don't do the same thing.
why why alone
Hmm
It's afternoon
I didn't invite you to the group chat room either.
people
Would you like to have a company dinner to tell you that you are leaving the company?
I don't even want it
Now
Our team finished the settlement well this time.
I passed the audit perfectly.
I got a golden salary from the company.
Because everyone had a hard time this time
Go to this
It's good, go eat a lot of delicious food
Huh, thank you
Stop eating pigs
Ah, let’s go somewhere else this time.
Then we
In the group chat room, everyone
If you want to eat it somewhere,
In group chat room
Please upload it straight up
Then let me summarize it.
Huh
What should I do?
It was beef
Can I eat beef?
ha
Now
tomorrow
What is the most important thing at the event?
right away
Seats will be arranged. Among them,
table number one
By name
Marron Zega’s VIP Table
In this place, there are many
As many executives attend
There will be a lot of attention.
right here
Who should be the main character?
Can you give me a dog? If so.
This common
Is it a fire street?
have something to talk about
I think the person would be nice
Oh, by the way, I
Expert and this high school
I am an alumni
I'm a college alumnus.
Jiwon is a local cam.
The team leader is the same.
Ah yes hehe
I'm in the same unit as you
Professional, you were exempt from military service.
I wish it had come out
No, but now everyone
Why do you want to sit at the table?
I'm just like that expert.
Isn’t it a bit burdensome?
Oh, I don't mind sitting anywhere.
Why are you sitting anywhere?
At table number one
Dr. Han will also sit down.
and we
There is also an unofficial team legend.
table number one
Those who embrace it will be promoted within a year.
Of course, I won't be interested again, but of course
Of course I also have to
He is a very wealthy person
I did
Okay, but tomorrow
Our Milktado business performance report
who has it
Oh, I have that.
But maybe
Should I give it to you now or not?
I'll give it to you right away
quickly quickly quickly quickly
Mr. Dong-gu
I haven't changed my clothes yet
Change quickly
The company is no joke
No, I just changed my clothes.
Just before that
The color is similar to the sanitary uniform.
Ah, how similar is it?
Don't be angry
Because it's that important day
I'm being honest.
Plus, eh
As I said again
It's a bit of a burdensome position.
A little like this
차려 입어야 하는 그런 에
So
That place is with me
It's not a suitable place
That's what you're saying, hehe
That's how important it is.
strange
In the meantime, I
There will be
I thought I knew the place well.
I have a different thought at this moment.
Something like that
Is it my part-time job?
Did you know?
I don't know. Let's just be fair.
Yes, sorry but
I’m also a bit greedy for that important position.
I was about to leave.
So what should I do?
There's only one way
If you don’t pay, you lose rock, paper, scissors
rock paper scissors rock paper scissors rock paper scissors
If you don’t pay, you lose, rock, paper, scissors
Dahye
Mr. Three times is also a treasure trove
Oh Jisung
You know that dress from earlier?
lend it to me
No, I'll just live there
Please help me instead
Okay
See you after work then
How about a Thai restaurant near your office?
They say it’s a golden meal, let’s eat something more expensive.
That's right, it's hot, let's go
But now I see it
Why is Jisung not in this room?
no
That's why I'll invite Jisung.
This is the accounting team chat room.
Oh now
You can forget about Tteokgal Ramen
salty
tomorrow's party
The main character will definitely be my sister.
Wow
Wow awesome
Hey
I'm okay
Oh, it's not good enough
So tomorrow too
You can do the same thing as you do now.
With hair and makeup
Because you saw what I did, sister.
you could do the same
Wait a minute, how can I do this by myself?
You have golden hands and I have dirty hands, yeah
Then what should I do?
Where should I lay the blanket?
Should I put it here or there?
Oh, I'm covering my legs.
Oh my, I’m laughing.
Put it here, yeah
tea tea tea
tea
Huh
I
Only you
Turtle, Suya
From ballads to children's songs
um
you
Just for you
Disappointing guitar
Romance attached
Why
Hey, what are you singing a dirge for?
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
Juman, why?
There's a girl I'm having a relationship with.
If you don't eat it once
How should I view this?
I don't think it's a flirtation.
If you want to have a flirtation
I think I need to eat
If you don't eat
I don't think it's a flirtation.
If you want to have a relationship, this conversation is
will repeat forever
I think it is
If you don't eat
You are right Mr. Lee
Let's stop, okay
I don't have any emotions
ok let's stop
just
Don't make a comeback, be satisfied with your first name.
Looking at it, Kitner2B
The number of views is huge and good.
Come on, 3.1 million
It's Jiwoo TV
I think you are just expensive
What if you just buy good tuna?
It's okay
What are you feeding me?
What you feeding me now is a bastard.
You, you, you, you, you fed it first.
Hey, I rent here.
Macbull Ramen per month
How many part-time jobs do you have?
I know I have to do it
Oh, I'm with you now
doing this
I'm a person who doesn't even waste time
Hey, what are you doing like that?
But what should I do if I want to have a relationship?
Does it work?
I'm going out. I'm not going out. I'm going out. I'm going out.
You bastard
go out go out
Get out you bastard
You bastard
Mr. Jisung
In knowing
Thanks to Jisung, we too
Let’s go somewhere hot
Ah, it’s been a while since our team’s group ceremony.
our team
Ah
Take off your makeup and take off your dress.
I'm watching the child
What
no
twelve o'clock
It’s like a magic that disappears when you hit it
Sister, I really am right now
I feel like Cinderella
No
Cinderella's magic
It ends at twelve o'clock
our magic
At twelve o'clock
salty
It went up again
It also rose by 50,000 won
Huh, awesome, awesome, awesome!
No talking about friends
don't hate it
Huh, that's while I'm on my cell phone
sister
Is Ji-seok really not going to join us?
Ah, the flow is perfect right now.
We'll see
You won't just leave it at that and not look at it.
Of course, I'm totally screwed.
Oh, I have to do something.
in the crazy house
Ah, if you look at me, you look like a mother.
Did your sister get upset?
It came out haha well
If I came out
I think it would have come out much better than that.
Look like me
Even if I can’t do it, I sell it
I just need to do a test
Is it Kim Ji-sung?
앞다마 금지
Well, my ears are bright again
uh
Wait a minute
Oh stop, what are you doing?
Do you talk that much?
Oh, I see.
our team
We're talking about something very important.
ha
It’s a hot place, I’m cracking up.
A steak called Listera in Seongsu-dong
It's a delicious restaurant
Just one bite is completely delicious.
a taste of heaven
Hannam-dong Rio
Risotto made by an Italian chef
It's art
Elo Kitchen in Yeonnam-dong
It takes half a year to make a reservation.
I always fail to make reservations too.
do you want to go there
You can go
What are you talking about?
Looks like tomorrow is already fully booked.
Mr. Jisung
It's not like I just said something without a plan.
Dinners are also an extension of work.
No, I go often and I’m a regular.
Then Jisung
The reservation will be made exactly as you said.
Awesome then
Jisung, a regular, has a dinner party here.
I guess I can make a reservation.
end end
Thank you Jisung
What are you doing?
You're a badass, right?
No, unless you're a bully
To tease people like this
You can't make it
But you're misunderstanding now.
I keep picking first and then eating.
When I asked to eat,
Right now
I think you misunderstand the situation.
For me, it was all courtesy.
No, it's not like that.
That kind of thing happens between a man and a woman.
on one side
one side like that
Because if you avoid it outright, it hurts.
So I became human
It was a bit kind of me.
If you just avoid it like that,
Oh, I can't hear you clearly. You're driving.
Yes ah
So
If you're not busy yet, let's meet up.
Ah, I need to clear up some misunderstandings.
I just finished
Because it’s near my house.
Where is it nearby?
Are you Sillim? Yes, Sillim.
Yeah, I happen to be there.
Oh, I'm like this again
I moved to Daebang-dong.
Yes, Daebang
Oh, I happen to be near that station.
If you look at it in reverse, it's Singil Station.
God I'm just there at the right time
finish
I don't know where you were
I'm with my friends right now.
yes guys
friend
friends
What are you an idol? Are you staying in a camp?
Why are we together until this time?
So let's meet tomorrow
tomorrow event
I'm going to sit next to Dr. Han.
We eat together
boss
If the speech gets too long, let's look at each other's scars together.
You don't like it
Ah
Oh just really
He asked me to eat out of courtesy.
I didn't notice
Why can’t I hear you?
what tomorrow
And that schedule
Because I don't know what will happen
For now, just a little
I need some time to think.
Oh that's right
Then think about it.
I like what you said
let's do that
Oh, you thought about it
I'm sorry I'll wait a long time
So let's meet tomorrow.
Please sit next to me
yes
See you tomorrow
Oh so cute
What is it? Why are you taking my name out?
Oh what is it
Why are you taking my name out, Mr. Dahee?
Yes ah yes
the boss
They say you’re attending.
Originally a business trip
He was on his way home but had to return home early.
But yeah
The child's boss did it unconditionally.
The doctor wants to sit next to you.
Because you did it
What place can I change?
There is only one seat for Dahee.
Now this is a bit like this
Where is something like that?
You have to sit as originally scheduled.
Yes then now boss
disobeying the word
No, rather than that
Oh my boss
somewhere in my place
here
Uh hahaha
Oh, sit down. Yes, sit down.
Ehehe ehehe
really
Isn't it possible? The reservations are already full.
my mother that
lifetime
Even if my wish is like this
Ah
I ended up
I guess it gave birth to this burn haha.
is my mother
You were adopted overseas when you were young.
So
Mushin, politician of the Cho Kuk Party
In a restaurant that feels like
This is an Italian restaurant.
Ah
It's only Italy
So, to Korea like this
You came for adoption
Haha, first of all, Tiamo
Grazia
Fuck it haha Fuck it haha
Just come back next time, boss.
I really
Just having a blast here
I need to have an oil party
Do you feel refreshed?
So I just became the boss
embarrass me
Just
What happened to the people who passed by?
And I just filmed a video.
I just put up my laptop and just put it on.
About me
The boss is just ingeupdong
I don't want to meet you as a star
Mom I'm sorry
no really really
We're really fully booked, sir.
Boss, one team was canceled at 7 o'clock.
Kim Ji-seong, seven o'clock this evening
Reservation for a total of six people.
no just now
He said he would eat it with his mother.
Oh, you made a reservation.
I don't know, hehehe ah
Me and if it's okay with you
With me
Can you please pretend to be friendly?
Well one
I come here five times a week
the most expensive
Eat the course like a meal
uh like that
An elegant guest
As if to say it exists haha yes
Mammam you crazy bitch haha
thank you
Yes, I made a reservation.
uh
I have time left, should I go to the department store?
Why do you go to the department store?
I couldn't do it earlier
I saw it to fit the interior.
I just have to say one thing, okay.
I was excited to even change a person’s nationality.
very uh
Baby, that's right
It was this expensive in the first place
Why do you lie and say you’re a regular at the restaurant?
That's that group chat
Trying to show off like this
What's left if you even lie?
What's left
photo
Update on S&S
Well, it's good.
company like this
Going around
Photos with people from the same team
one sheet
Taking pictures like this
I don't think it's bad
It's pretty in a place like this
I pretended to take a picture and uploaded it to S&S.
That photo really feels like your life
real life
It's outside of that picture, Jisung.
Hey, what do you want to say?
So stop bragging
Now for real
Let's live a proper life
together with us
Don't talk about Hoin's makeup.
I really won't listen
I don't listen
I don't listen, I don't listen, I don't listen
I hate it I hate it I don’t listen
I don't listen, I don't listen
Hoin
That burn is real
Ah, but why hasn’t the child contacted me?
I don't know if I'm doing well
Wow
Maron Confectionery Let’s live forever Maron
Let's go together Maron
I love you Maron hahahaha
I love you
Maron Maron Maron
Hey, our Dr. Han
You're killing the screen
It's your child
I also once
I heard you look like an actor.
I know Jang Gu-gyeong
long bore
I was once a general in Gaepo-dong.
Insulting the deceased
No but
This
The table seems a little different.
There is this flower
Only my seat has cushions.
That's right
As if someone had prepared something
Haha
Everyone, that
Have you seen the movie Father before?
You, Jang Gu-gyeong, are there.
Where did you sit
I'm sitting in Gaepo-dong, Jang Gu-gyeong.
Oh, raise your hand and say yes?
Ms. Dahye
Oh yes
This place is empty
Oh yes hehe
But
Dahye, number one today
on the table
You didn't decide to sit down.
Why did the boss do that?
Oh, but Da-hye sits in the front.
why are you here
I want to be with Dahye.
Haha, more with Dahye.
I want to become friends
Hahahaha yes what
It would be nice to become friends
Our award later
When I go to get it
We can go up together, right?
Oh right, award
Yes, let’s go up together, yes
Next is the temple
To encourage your hard work
There will be time to award awards.
Then, I will name the winner right away.
The winner is Dahee Jeong of the marketing team.
Yoon Jun-seo and Jeong Da-hye
Due to time constraints
The award is represented by Dahee Jeong.
I will let you win the award.
Dahee Jeong
Oh Jeong Da-hee Jeong Da-hee Jeong Da-hee Nice
Oh, please come up to the stage quickly.
Oh that's it
that
what are you doing
Get up quickly, Dahee.
You're calling me
I love you Jeong Da-hee
Milky color Jeong Da-hee
Woooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
oh
Fourteen Period
the warmth of your colleagues
Even the cheering was so heartwarming
This is the scene
Come up here on stage
I would appreciate it if you could take a look
Next, there will be an award ceremony.
Excellence Award for Work Attitude: Jeong Da-hee’s Lee In
Kia is sincere
Working attitude and responsible attitude
Doing work
It was an encouragement to my colleagues
Geared towards the company's development
In recognition of the state
Awarded an award
uh
Originally, I thought we all received it together.
With such meaningful words
It's really nice to receive reviews
I'm glad
especially
You are generous to me, who is always lacking.
Oh my oh my oh my oh my
Ah
ha
one dress
Ah ah what is it
Why are you coming in here?
Because they didn't reply
You don't reply
Let’s get out quickly. What are you doing?
You're avoiding me
Well, I can't even see your face
Oh, it's not like that.
It's because of some circumstances.
So what is the situation?
Oh, that's really true
Why are you like this? Why are you like that?
IC
This suddenly gives me a nosebleed
Teacher, it’s all right.
yes
So
Because you did me wrong
I'm being punished
wow
What did I do wrong?
Then it's not wrong
This is how people feel
It makes me burn
What are you saying?
I'm really showing off right now
You wouldn't know it if you looked at it
Mistress is awesome
It's like this
Lifting and dropping people like this
I sit with the CEO.
I saw it there
Wow, I was jealous
So, that's it.
Let's take a break here
Oh good
Ah
It's uncomfortable. This isn't Dahye's seat.
Where did you go?
It was originally table number one.
I changed it earlier and it went somewhere else.
I saw Dahye today
They put a lot of effort into decorating it.
Dahye and I are sitting together.
It was a bit funny
Dahye is white
wearing a dress
I'm with Dahye.
A little bit of this flatfish
Like an angel underneath
What is skidashi?
Mr. Jiwon, skiing again?
Let's write Korean side dishes haha
What the heck, didn't you just move?
Something was moving
uh uh surprise
What is this?
Oh why why why why what
Is there anyone in there?
Uh, is there anyone?
There's someone in there
For now, turn around
Turn around, what, what, what, turn around
turn now
Oh, I'm going to turn around. What should I really do?
straight ahead
What should I do? Where should I go?
Turn left Turn left Turn left
Let's go, keep going
Uh rain
Get out of the way, get out of the way, stop, stop
uh uh
Oh, I hit it. It seems to have disappeared.
Where is the door?
It's over there, it's crazy, it's over there
run run
Wait a minute, kill me, kill me
kill it
kill me one more time
Where is it? There is an emergency exit.
oh oh
Oh oh oh oh
I'm all here, now Mr. Aw
All you have to do is get past here.
Cheer up a little bit
That person whose hands and feet don't fit together
Oh you shit
uh
Team leader now
Likewise, what are you doing here?
Ah, this is all for a reason.
Why is the owner of the factory, Kim Kim, calling?
I don't accept it
twenty now
I heard you called me more than a dozen times. Yes.
call me
Oh, what's going on? What's going on?
snacks now
Baeksang is now
They say it was delivered somewhere completely different.
what happened
Company here
How on earth did you give me the address?
yes
Oh, Dahye contacted the delivery company.
Dahye is the winner.
Have a deep conversation with the boss now
We are sharing
I know it pitifully well
I've been doing this a lot
Our employees went there
i am that
Mr. Ddongko takes care of everything.
Shouldn't it have been sorted out?
Now the kids and their guardians have already
I arrived
what are you going to do
Oh my, me too
award
Oh really
sorry
Oh really Mr.
how do i talk
Let's go
The next bath is the study bath.
That
It's okay
yes what
I'm a little embarrassed
Other than that it’s okay haha
On the contrary, it's a bit funny.
me now
I was completely screwed haha.
It's not that funny
Why is it funny haha
I think it's funny
yes
I actually don’t find it funny either.
Just a little
You can't just laugh it off
I can't believe I'm like this
Like this to get hurt
Even wearing a nice dress
It wouldn't have come
Me too
I was kind of expecting something.
That was my greed in the end
that
I was seen by people with different feelings
crab
Oh really
So so so much
I feel like I'm going to turn away because I'm embarrassed.
So just laugh a little
He said he would pass it on.
What's going on?
What did you really expect?
Yes, what did you expect?
What did you want to become?
Maybe
Well, am I the main character here?
I guess that's right
Ha, now it's a bit funny
what are you talking about
something
I think you're thinking wrong
Oh, that's right
a nice dress
You become the main character by wearing it.
stunning
You have to do something to become the main character.
But in reality, Dahye Jeong
Haven't you done anything yet?
But what's embarrassing?
I
What can I do? Anything
If you miss, you'll hit it
I'm not working hard
If anything happens
turn the table over
I'm a person who can write and jump.
Listen, listen to the table.
I'll do anything to do it
In my opinion, that is
Wherever you are
He seems like someone who can make it on stage.
at that moment
I remembered
Dahyeya
Haha mom
When did you come?
I saw it, I saw it, then how did I see it?
I was in the corner of the stage over there.
All I could see was my daughter.
wherever you are
The brightest and coolest
Really yes
Actually I wasn't just standing there
I did some acting
I'm shaking in the wind
I want to see you
How about it, I'm good at it, I'm the best
Uhhhh
wherever i am
A person who can look cool no matter how messy his hair is
With that dress
A person who dare not prove
a person who can do anything
No, it was like that before too
What kind of Bukcheong did I just see over there?
I thought you were playing with Mr. Sajanori.
No, we're perfect
I heard it was a cultural asset of dance.
Restaurant Yes, where is the restaurant?
Restaurant on the first floor of the basement
Ah
please help me
I'll try anything
Hey please visit
It hurts
Guys, it hurts, stop it, stop it
cucumber
Hello, let’s just do one part-time job, okay?
that's my wish
Working just one part-time job
I have to go serve now.
Hey, this is my music
When will the world unfold?
that world
I'll let this super common dragon unfold
bounce
uh
uh intelligence
Dinner for Mr.
Let's not say we moved the location.
Anyway, this is Kim Ji-seong’s regular restaurant.
We can go next time.
Aha
Ah, but that's a bit much
Honestly that
The restaurant is weak
Because we want to go
I feel like I'm weak
I was secretly invited to the group chat room.
Looks like you like it
Oh stop, what are you doing?
Do you talk that much?
Oh, I see.
our team
We're talking about something very important.
Always in group chat room
Post things that make you laugh
I say hello every now and then.
I'm just watching
Jidochi said it was afternoon.
Isn't it walking on the team?
Oh honestly I
Why Kim Ji-seon?
In our group chat room
I don't even know if I invited you
this team
We did a good job receiving the incense.
no
Oh, what did he say on that topic?
Then I will
Ah ah ah
Oh, what are you doing?
Oh sorry
ha
Ha really
Ah, Kang Eun-sang is a pathetic human being.
Without knowing anything
They say they are good and put them in a disciplinary room.
Oh, why isn't he answering the phone?
Maylin, where am I now?
salty
I'm having a dinner party today
Wow
I hope, baby, it’s really pretty there.
Our Jisung’s face is prettier, he’s beautiful
Oh wait a minute
Hmm
Oh baby
When you come to Korea, let's come here together, yeah
It's really pretty here hmm
Now children
I'm really sorry
To you today
The taste of pork cutlet I wanted to give as a gift
Don Don Chips
To the main creditor
Today due to unforeseen circumstances
I can't give it to you
But
Let's take a moment
Please give me the microphone.
Why is this guitar
used as an interlude
showcase
in people
I change the channel and spread the blanket
I don't care about that
What is Dr. Han’s song?
You're pretty good at it
But this song
us
I thought he was listening to you on the tube.
That's right, my nephew too, right?
This popped up in my algorithm shop.
Wow the kids really like it
I was patient haha
Oh my, I'm dying
Oh my
Let’s do it one more time. It’s the best. It’s the best.
Oh my gosh, do it one more time
You have to do it one more time
Pork cutlet taste
If snacks don't work
You should at least use real pork cutlet.
Pork cutlet set meal for 30 people
No, it's great
No, how did you come up with all these thoughts?
There's nothing I can't do
Thank goodness
Thank you, Dahee.
Mr. Dahee
Otherwise, I would be scared of the group at my house.
I almost broke it
Thanks to you, I survived
The menu at the county restaurant was good.
Finally, pork cutlet came out as a side dish.
Today is really
The rib side dish was great, wasn’t it?
I really did it before
Then I guess it's Park Geun-hye
I was surprised
I saw you singing loudly earlier.
i am me
that bruno mars
I thought it was an ocean country.
Ah, Michang Children’s Bruno Mars
Jiwoo Ham Mas Mas
Ah, it seems a bit Japanese.
Anyway
guest
I heard this is the last one coming
Ah
Yes haha
That's enough
It's obvious anyway
What are you doing by asking?
Hey, let’s eat, let’s eat, baby, what’s expensive?
I'll eat, hey, hey, let's sleep.
Now, wait a minute, just a moment, not yet
Jisung didn’t come.
Baby I
I'll send you a message here right away.
Oh wait
uh
Oh, why is everyone in the chatroom?
You went out
Ah
Oh that
Ah, now that I think about it
Everyone has a private life
Is it necessary to create a group chat room?
Because I want to
Necessary business
If I have it, I'm going to text it now.
No, but if you do this, Jiyong is here
Oh, I'll make a quick call.
Ah
Ji-seong Kim
I went to meet my boyfriend today.
Oh, you called me without notice
Ah
Oh yes, that's right
Let's just eat by ourselves.
Yes yes shall we salty?
Yes haha ah, salty salty
Please
salty
Jisung Kim Jisungah
sister
Oh, you have to pay, why are you here?
you are here now
I also eat pasta
I also ate pizza
And drink wine
Get the shot of your life
You will be very full and happy.
ha
This girl is very hungry right now.
Where are you going?
Let's eat something
uh
Why
I ate a lot so I'm full.
It's because I'm hungry
Ah
Oh, what are you going to eat?
Oh, I think Dokwan went out.
Ah, sister, sister, sister
Ah
Oh, it's so hard
um
The food is delicious, no matter what.
Of course Korean food is the best, yeah
That's right
No, but
Why do you risk your life for a company dinner like that?
workplace
What is eating together with colleagues?
It's so big
You eat with us all the time too.
um
The sisters are not coworkers
Because they are my family
Oh and
really
It's good to get along well with your colleagues.
What
It's not like we can live as enemies like this.
It's not
They also invited me to a group chat room, so I
They are like me too
I thought it was my heart
Hmm
I'm just watching
Instructor
It's afternoon
Isn't it walking on the team?
You mean that
oh
Oh Ji-song is coming
Try some stir-fried squid
This is delicious haha
eat
Oh, I didn't even know that
Me and Dahye non-deductible
How can I be deceived when I talk to myself?
I would have burned it
that
oh
Oh what
Where should I get plastic surgery to look pretty haha
That kid is pretty too haha
Oh what
What what
What do you want to say? Yeah.
So
oh
Among them
in front of virtual
The market's upward trend is unusual.
Various coins are increasing day by day.
Recording a rise in width
Focus the attention of investors
There is
Enderion is especially strong.
Let’s look at today’s date chart.
wow enderion
uh
uh uh
rice cake table
I lost my job and got a job right away.
I don't want to do music anymore
Wow
At that time, I sold my guitar and bought shoes.
inside those shoes
stone
I felt like I was stepping on one.
Rolling around here and there
My feet keep getting wet
나는 그게 꼭 음악 같더라고
That's me
It's definitely true that it hurts
I don't have the confidence to take it out
That's right
There is no smoke from flipping your shoes over.
Like a stone
By stepping on one, I reached here
It came
Dahye Jeong's dress
It's like your shoes to me
It's expensive and cool, but I wore it.
Not the main character
I'm not yet
Where I really want to be
What I really want
I couldn't do it
That's it
how expensive
It was shoes and makeup.
Have you heard that before? Expensive shoes.
Haha
Me, though.
Still got those things once
I miss you
The dress that Song Hye-kyo wore
The car that Jeon Ji-yeon drives
Um, again, the apartment where Kim Tae-hee lives.
The real protagonists
Even without that
That he is a wonderful person
I understand it in my head.
But my heart is still
um
gift
I guess it's obvious
Haha next time
I have to take it to a really expensive place.
Oh there is also next time
Then there is no next time
What are you, you idiot? Haha.
Let’s go now, let’s go already
Oh, just a little more
Oh my
Let’s have a cup of coffee in front of there.
Oh, it's almost time for the last train
Mmmmmmmmm
But what
If you can take me there
Then I
I'll run with you all the way to here.
100 meters 12 seconds
Gunner is so fast, shoo shoo swoosh
Even if you hit the jackpot, you will definitely see it at times like this.
What is it
There is no separate leaf
gourd
What kind of kid is Jjopak?
Wait a minute kid
No, but from earlier
Why do you keep doing this?
Are you uncomfortable?
no
I felt like something was in my shoes.
What's wrong with those expensive shoes?
Ah
Please shake off the phone and come back.
Oh hello rice cake
Oh, I'm surprised.
Dahye, oh Dahye, it’s a rice cake table.
Oh, wait, just hang up for a second.
Huh, what should I do?
Uh huh
I'm afraid it's like this
yes
I'm afraid you'll run away like this
I just endured it
I want to keep walking together
Dr. Han
What the hell
Why to me
Why would you do that?
why would i do that
Dahyeya
The stone in Dr. Han's shoe
It rolled into my heart
It's clear
But the sound of stones rolling
Isn’t it a lot of fun?
Why do I always hear my heart pounding?
Ha no
This is it
It's because the coin has gone up.
It's all because of the coins
that
We also eat together with our team members.
What do you usually eat?
Is the pork cutlet not that good?
Oh, I like pork cutlet.
Sometimes at lunch
There are times when we all go out to eat together.
I like it
Wow, Namsan is really perfect then.
child
But it's a bit far to go for lunch.
Oh well
Tonkatsu
Who should like it?
Maybe
Mr. shit
shit post
Oh, that's Dahye's nickname.
It's like a nickname or something.
Dahye Jeong’s nickname is shit, why?
Is this shit post a shit post?
It's really funny no
No, no matter how you look at it
I'm not the round type, but my personality is
And when I get angry
First of all, I tear people down with these eyes.
It's like it's going to kill me
uh like that
It's Mungtaju.
Well I don't know
What is that human
But I don't have any other nicknames.
No, your expression is perfect right now.
Hey, take a quick picture, quickly take a picture
That expression now
It's that love
That thing I love
I don’t think it’s a company, director.
At that moment with my sisters
I'm going out, I'm out
real cell phone
our money
once
You came here to use it properly.
It’s okay to have this kind of flex once in a while
Hey, it's pretty good.
again
If you say coin, they just go to each other.
Give me your hand
Ah
I'll just keep it until tonight.
Hey, I'm not here.
So
Why did you take away all your cell phones?
Oh, what are you doing, sister?
And then what happens if you get screwed?
The trip is going to be a disaster like this.
Please save me
Mr. Dahye
Dahye
Mr.